const trivia = [
  {
    question: "What battle was fought in 1066 which was won on this day?",
    answers: ["Battle of Stamford Bridge", "Battle of Hastings", "Battle of Norman", "The Battle for England"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which Revolutinary War hero was captured on this day?",
    answers: ["Ethan Allen", "Thomas Jefferson", "George Washington", "Franklin D. Roosevelt"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which army officer defects to the British during the Revolutionary War on this day in 1780?",
    answers: ["Benedict Arnold", "Nathanael Greene", "Henry Knox", "Benjamin Lincoln"]
  },
  {
    question: "Was the Bill of Rights proposed on this date?",
    answers: ["Yes", "No", "No, but it was drafted on this date", "No, but it was voted upon this date"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which amendment to the Constitution became effective on this date?",
    answers: ["12th", "11th", "10th", "13th"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which two countries sign a disarment treaty on this date in 1340?",
    answers: ["England and France", "England and Ireland", "England and the United States", "Mexico and the United States"]
  },
  {
    question: "In 1513 which ocean did the Spaish explorer Vasco Núñez de Balboa explore on this date?",
    answers: ["Pacific Ocean", "Atlantic Ocean", "Indian Ocean", "Arctic Ocean"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which year was the first printing press set up in Cambridge on this date?",
    answers: ["1639", "1529", "1765", "1694"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which two countries sign a trade agreement on this date in 1654?",
    answers: ["England and Denmark", "England and Ireland", "England and France", "The United States and England"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which two countries sign a disarment treaty on this date in 1340?",
    answers: ["England and France", "England and Ireland", "England and the United States", "Mexico and the United States"]
  },
  {
    question: "Whose assassination attempt failed on this date in 1829?",
    answers: ["On Simon Bolívar", "On George Washington", "On John Quincy Adams", "On Andrew Jackson"]
  },
  {
    question: "Where was the first cricket match hosted on this date in 1844?",
    answers: ["In New York", "In England", "In Toronto", "In California"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which territory did the US begin occupying on this date in 1846?",
    answers: ["Monterey", "Seattle", "Vancouver", "Mexico City"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which fugitive escapes jail on this date in 1875?",
    answers: ["Billy the Kid", "Jack the Ripper", "Jesse James", "John Wilkes Booth"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which national park is established on this date in 1890 by Benjamin Harrison?",
    answers: ["Seqoia National Park", "Yellowstone National Park", "North Cascades National Park", "Olympic National Park"]
  },
  {
    question: "What year did the first British bus service begin on this date?",
    answers: ["1897", "1880", "1901", "1924"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which two countries sign a disarment treaty on this date in 1340?",
    answers: ["England and France", "England and Ireland", "England and the United States", "Mexico and the United States"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which President suffers a breakdown on this date in 1919?",
    answers: ["Woodrow Wilson", "Franklin D. Roosevelt", "William Howard Taft", "Warren G. Harding"]
  },
  {
    question: "What was the world auto speed record set by Malcolm Campbell on this date in 1924?",
    answers: ["146.16mph", "120.15mph", "100.12mph", "90.37mph"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which company announces the 40-hour work week on this date in 1926?",
    answers: ["Ford Motor Company", "US Steel", "Standard Oil", "DuPont"]
  },
  {
    question: "What year on this date was the international slavery convention signed by 20 states?",
    answers: ["1920", "1925", "1926", "1896"]
  },
  {
    question: "What year did Billy Graham begin his LA Crusade on this date?",
    answers: ["1947", "1949", "1951", "1943"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which nuclear test occured on this date in 1962?",
    answers: ["Novaya Zemlya in the USSR", "Kamchatka Oblast in the USSR", "Hawaiian Coast in the US", "New Mexican Test Site in the US"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which major nuclear test occured on this date in 1974?",
    answers: ["Nevada Test Site in the US", "Arizona Test Site in the US", "Kamchatka Oblast in the USSR", "Moscow Oblast in the USSR"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which 1st female Supreme Court Justice was sworn in on this day in 1981?",
    answers: ["Sandra Day O'Connor", "Ruth Bader Ginsburg", "Sonia Sotomayor", "Ketanji Brown Jackson"]
  }
];
